Contact

toya2xcel@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/latoyacabbell-bsn-rn-cmsrn-0506861b (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

CPR Certified

Vital Signs

Patient Care

Certifications

Basic Life Support for Healthcare Providers (BLS)

Registered Nurse

COVID-19 Contact Tracing

Interpersonal Communication

Certified Medical-Surgical Registered Nurse (CMSRN)

LaToya Cabbell, BSN, RN, CMSRN

Bachelors of Science in Nursing at Virginia Commonwealth University

Richmond, Virginia Area

Summary

A compassionate Registered Nurse with 4-years of experience looking to gain additional experience and knowledge and to utilize my skills in a manner that would provide safe and exemplary care to patients and their families. A productive, efficient and independent healthcare professional who is responsive and attentive to patient needs. Superb communication, interpersonal, organizational and time management skills. Experience with ensuring high standards of culturally competent care for a wide variety of patients with diverse needs.

Experience

HCA Healthcare

5 years 1 month

Registered Nurse, Charge Nurse June 2016 - June 2020 (4 years 1 month)

- Conducted individualized physical assessments for inpatient general surgery patients pre- and post-operatively, trauma patients, medical patients and transplant patients.
- Provided appropriate bedside patient care and interventions per facility policy for 5-6 patients per shift.
- Administered all medications utilizing rights to medication administration and knowledge of pharmacokinetics with no medication errors.
- Initiated and documented patient teaching and discharge planning in collaboration with multidisciplinary team members.
- Trained and mentored new graduate nurses, tasking their patient care duties and overseeing the results.
- Oversaw daily functioning of the unit directing admissions, discharges and general patient flow. Assigned nurses and support staff to patient care while meeting the daily goals of the unit.
- Strong reputation for achieving high levels of patient satisfaction.

Page 1 of 3

StaRN Graduate RN

June 2016 - July 2016 (2 months)

12-week program for nursing graduates that combined classroom instruction, an extensive simulation experience and hands-on clinical training. Over 60 hours of high-fidelity simulation including comprehensive debriefs.

Patient Care Technician

June 2015 - June 2016 (1 year 1 month)

Richmond, Virginia Area

- Provided direct patient care under the supervision of a Registered Nurse.
- Duties included: to take vital signs and assist patients with activities of daily living including feeding, personal hygiene, grooming and ambulation. Obtained blood glucose checks and changed bed linens. Delivered specimens and retrieved blood products from the lab.
- Assisted in admission, transfer, and discharge of patients.
- Observed isolation precautions, safety policies and answered call lights.
- Accurately documented all care provided and intake and output measurements.

WellPoint

Customer Care Representative

February 2013 - August 2014 (1 year 7 months)

Responded to inquiries from brokers, group administrators and internal Anthem representatives in reference to group employee enrollments in Anthem Health Insurance.

Xerox Healthcare Solutions

Customer Service Representative

April 2010 - August 2012 (2 years 5 months)

Fiscal Agent for the Department of Medical Assistance Services who responded to healthcare provider inquiries about provider enrollment, member eligibility, electronic data interchange, webportal technical support and complex claims/billing questions pertaining to Virginia Medicaid.

Comcast

Customer Account Executive

June 2006 - February 2010 (3 years 9 months)

Answered inbound calls to process customer payments and addressed billing inquires with a 75% first call resolution rate.

Transitioned on calls to offer additional products and services which led to a 5% sales close rate.

Troubleshot customer cable equipment via the telephone with a 70% resolution rate.

Peebles Department Store

Sales Associate

June 2001 - October 2006 (5 years 5 months)

Provided a welcoming, pleasing store environment while displaying knowledge of company merchandise.

Money handling, store upkeep and created eye-catching display.

Second highest customer service score in the region award 2002.

Education

Virginia Commonwealth University

Bachelors of Science in Nursing, Registered Nursing/Registered

Nurse · (2017 - 2019)

J Sargeant Reynolds Community College
Associate of Applied Science in Nursing Degree, Registered Nursing/
Registered Nurse · (2014 - 2016)

James Madison University Health Science · (2003 - 2006)